the sense of
presence is almost
like when you're
designing something that's
sort of trying
to artificially deliver
it, you're delivering
an illusion to
a person.
And more than
any one thing
that provides a
sense of presence,
it's actually more
the case that
any one thing
done wrong breaks
the sense
of presence.
You kind of
know that you're
interacting with technology,
but it's so
convincing that
you just kind
of go along
with it, and
you're like, "Okay,
yeah, no, this
person feel like
they're there," right?
when I did
that ping pong
demo, like at
the end of
it, I dropped
the ping pong
paddle on the
virtual table and
it shattered, so
that was not
the best for
our internal
development.
But like that's
winning in our
development, right? It's
like when you
feel like something
is kind of
so realistic that
you're just convinced
that